Guide to the International Typographical Union Local 99 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- RECORD GROUP B: INTERNATIONAL TYPOGRAPHICAL UNION LOCAL 202 SEATTLE, 1908-1978 (Box-folder 4/1-47/1, 69-73)
  - SERIES VII: MINUTES - EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1907-1974 (Box-folder 19/1-19/101)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1961 (Box-folder 19/75)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1961 (Box-folder 19/76)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1962 (Box-folder 19/77)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1962 (Box-folder 19/78)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1963 (Box-folder 19/79)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1963 (Box-folder 19/80)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1964 (Box-folder 19/81)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1964 (Box-folder 19/82)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1965 (Box-folder 19/83)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1965 (Box-folder 19/84)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1966 (Box-folder 19/85)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1966 (Box-folder 19/86)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1967 (Box-folder 19/87)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1967 (Box-folder 19/88)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1968 (Box-folder 19/89)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1968 (Box-folder 19/90)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1969 (Box-folder 19/91)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1969 (Box-folder 19/92)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1970 (Box-folder 19/93)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1970 (Box-folder 19/94)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1971 (Box-folder 19/95)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1971 (Box-folder 19/96)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1972 (Box-folder 19/97)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1972 (Box-folder 19/98)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-June 1973 (Box-folder 19/99)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, July-December 1973 (Box-folder 19/100)
    - Executive Committee International Typographical Union, Local 99 International Typographical Union, Local 202 Minutes, January-May 1974 (Box-folder 19/101)
  - SERIES VIII: MINUTES - TELEGRAPH CHAPEL (SEATTLE), 1892-1894 (Box-folder BOX 66)
    - Minutes, Telegraph Chapel (Seattle), 1892-1894 (Box-folder 66 (Flat box))
  - SERIES IX: STRIKE FILES - SEATTLE-TACOMA JOINT STRIKE COMMITTEE, 1907-1977 (Box-folder 20/1-24/46)
    - Official Report of Proceedings Before the National Labor Relations Board, Part 1, 1960 (Box-folder 20/1)
    - Official Report of Proceedings Before the National Labor Relations Board, Part 2, 1960 (Box-folder 20/2)
    - Miscellaneous Letters Regarding Joint Strike Program, etc., 1961-1963 (Box-folder 20/3)
    - {Progress Report on the Auburn Citizen}, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 20/4)
    - Valley Publishing Company Label Case, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 20/5)
    - Fournier vs. Seattle-Tacoma 12-24-64, 1965 (Box-folder 20/6)
    - Kent News Journal Strike-May 22, 1962, 1946-1962 (Box-folder 20/7)
    - Valley Publishing Company National Labor Relations Board, 1970 (Box-folder 20/8)
    - David Hibbard, 1962 (Box-folder 20/9)
    - Richard A Marcelle, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 20/10)
    - Union-Kent, 1960-1970 (Box-folder 20/11)
    - Kent-International Typographical Union-The Newspaper Guild 1976 (Box-folder 20/12)
    - Kent 1974, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 20/13)
    - Organizational Program, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 21/1)
    - {Seattle Typographical Union letters}, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 21/2)
    - {Seattle Area Typographical Union Newspaper Clippings and letters}, 1964 (Box-folder 21/3)
    - Report to International Typographical Union, 1964 (Box-folder 21/4)
    - Sign-In Lynnwood, 1958-1965 (Box-folder 21/5)
    - Sign-In Renton, 1964 (Box-folder 21/6)
    - Original Schedule Copy, c.1965 (Box-folder 21/7)
    - Shop Schedules, 1965 (Box-folder 21/8)
    - Guilty Pleas-Violation of Duty of Membership, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 21/9)
    - Lockout Prosecution Charges, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 21/10)
    - Community and Civic Clubs, 1963 (Box-folder 21/11)
    - Mailing Lists of Local Unions, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 21/12)
    - Handbill Helps, c.1959-1965 (Box-folder 21/13)
    - Mailing Piece, c.1965 (Box-folder 21/14)
    - Mailing lists, c. 1960s (Box-folder 21/15)
    - Mailing Piece Extra, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 21/16)
    - Queen Anne-John Murray, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 21/17)
    - Grocery Boys, etc., 1965 (Box-folder 21/18)
    - Seattle-Tacoma Joint Committee, 1960-1965 (Box-folder 21/19)
    - Newspapers, Letters, Part 1, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 21/20)
    - Newspapers, Letters, Part 2, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 21/21)
    - Newspapers, Letters, Part 3, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 21/22)
    - Arbitration, The Newspaper Guild, Part 1, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 21/23)
    - Arbitration, The Newspaper Guild, Part 2, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 21/24)
    - The Manual of Linotype Typography, 1923 (Box-folder 21/25)
    - Answers and Personal Information, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 22/1)
    - Letters to Kenny Dale Employees, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 22/2)
    - Labor Dispute; Press Release/Publicity, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 22/3)
    - Misc. Joint Strike Committee, 1963 (Box-folder 22/4)
    - Negotiations, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 22/5)
    - National Labor Relations Board Case #19-CA-2043 Bellevue-Renton Report, 1967 (Box-folder 22/6)
    - Bellevue Bargaining; Burnett, 1961-1966 (Box-folder 22/7)
    - Bellevue Bogle, Bogle and Gates *Renton, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 22/8)
    - Prospectors for a Second Bellevue Newspaper, 1964 (Box-folder 22/9)
    - Bellevue-Renton Correspondence, Part 1 of 3, 1959-1967 (Box-folder 22/10)
    - Bellevue-Renton Correspondence, Part 2 of 3, 1959-1967 (Box-folder 22/11)
    - Bellevue-Renton Correspondence, Part 3 of 3, 1959-1967 (Box-folder 22/12)
    - Civil Action File Renton-Bellevue Wages and Dues Lost, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 22/13)
    - Civil Action File Renton-Bellevue Correspondence-Lockout, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 22/14)
    - Civil Action File Renton-Bellevue STU File-Coad, etc., 1960 (Box-folder 22/15)
    - Bellevue American Renton News Record, 1961-1973 (Box-folder 22/16)
    - Hearing Pay AFL-CIO on Bellevue, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 22/17)
    - Seattle-Tacoma Joint Strike Comm, 1962-1966 (Box-folder 22/18)
    - $250,000 Lawsuit Seattle Typographical Union vs Renton Record-Chronicle John Fournier, Part 1 of 2, 1965 (Box-folder 22/19)
    - $250,000 Lawsuit Seattle Typographical Union vs Renton Record-Chronicle John Fournier, Part 2 of 2, 1965 (Box-folder 22/20)
    - Lockout--1960-- New #1, Part 1 of 2, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 22/21)
    - Lockout--1960-- New #1, Part 2 of 2, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 22/22)
    - Lockout-1961-New #2, Part 1 of 5, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 22/23)
    - Lockout-1961-New #2, Part 2 of 5, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 22/24)
    - Lockout-1961-New #2, Part 3 of 5, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 22/25)
    - Lockout-1961-New #2, Part 4 of 5, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 22/26)
    - Lockout-1961-New #2, Part 5 of 5, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 22/27)
    - $250,000 Lawsuit, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 23/1)
    - Misc. Joint Strike Committee, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 23/2)
    - Seattle-Tacoma Joint Strike Program, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 23/3)
    - Seattle-Tacoma Joint Strike Program Confidential Reports, 1962 (Box-folder 23/4)
    - Photographs Lynnwood Enterprise Strike, 1961 (Box-folder 23/5)
    - Reports to International Typographical Union, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 23/6)
    - Bellevue-Renton Lockout 1960, Part 1 of 2, 1955-1971 (Box-folder 23/7)
    - Bellevue-Renton Lockout 1960, Part 2 of 2, 1955-1971 (Box-folder 23/8)
    - Amalgamated Lithographers of America (ALA), 1960-1968 (Box-folder 23/9)
    - Mailers Union, 1936-1975 (Box-folder 23/10)
    - Northwest Typographical Membership Committee, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 23/11)
    - National Labor Relations Board Case # 19-UC-92197, Part 1 of 2, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 23/12)
    - National Labor Relations Board Case # 19-UC-92197, Part 2 of 2, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 23/13)
    - Seattle-Tacoma Merger NW #99; Burnett, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 23/14)
    - B.O Gayle-National Labor Relations Board-1977 (Box-folder 23/15)
    - National Labor Relations Board-Barrington O. Gayle, 1975 (Box-folder 23/16)
    - Barrington Gayle Charges and Trials, 1967-1975 (Box-folder 23/17)
    - National Labor Relations Board Case #19-CB-2713 Hatten, Beverly, 1976 (Box-folder 23/18)
    - NLRB Case No.19-CB-2466, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 23/19)
    - National Labor Relations Board Case #19-RM-999 Cone-Heiden Corp. Local 45-L, LPIU/STU 202, 1972 (Box-folder 23/20)
    - Federal Way - Decertification, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 23/21)
    - Mid-Cities National Labor Relations Board, Part 1 of 2, 1973 (Box-folder 23/22)
    - Mid-Cities National Labor Relations Board, Part 2 of 2, 1973 (Box-folder 23/23)
    - United States Circuit Court of Appeals for the Ninth Circuit No. 1617 Transcript of Record, 1908 (Box-folder 23/24)
    - {Letters from various unions to employers and members}, 1929-1974 (Box-folder 24/1)
    - Special Form on Employing Printers' Association Proposal to Reduce Scale, 1932 (Box-folder 24/2)
    - P-1 Over Time Case, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 24/3)
    - {Letters, Reports and Petitions to and from union members}, 1934-1959 (Box-folder 24/4)
    - Ziegner, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 24/5)
    - School for Apprentices, 1930 (Box-folder 24/6)
    - {Letters about union dues}, 1921-1935 (Box-folder 24/7)
    - Coordination Committee, 1957 (Box-folder 24/8)
    - Hesselberg, Al "arrears", 1933-1934 (Box-folder 24/9)
    - Times Dispute Local Overtime Law, 1939-1955 (Box-folder 24/10)
    - 10% Assessment Objections-1921, 1921-1923 (Box-folder 24/11)
    - 44 Hour Strike Notices 1921 (Box-folder 24/12)
    - Coulthard (Ex. Comm) vs 12 Retained" Seattle Post Intelligencer Employees, 1928 (Box-folder 24/13)
    - {Letters, Newspapers and Magazines}, Part 1 of 2, 1928-1973 (Box-folder 24/14)
    - {Letters, Newspapers and Magazines}, Part 2 of 2, 1928-1973 (Box-folder 24/15)
    - Negotiations 1959, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 24/16)
    - {Newspapers and Newsletters}, 1965-1972 (Box-folder 24/17)
    - Newspaper Preservation Act, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 24/18)
    - The Typographical Journal, 1968 (Box-folder 24/19)
    - Snoqualmie Valley Record, 1962-1973 (Box-folder 24/20)
    - {Letters to Officers and Members of Seattle Typography Union}, Part 1 of 2, 1907-1939 (Box-folder 24/21)
    - {Letters to Officers and Members of Seattle Typography Union}, Part 2 of 2, 1907-1939 (Box-folder 24/22)
    - Gale, Norman, 1927-1928 (Box-folder 24/23)
    - {Letters to Seattle Typography Members}, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 24/24)
    - M. H. Rogers, 1928-1929 (Box-folder 24/25)
    - {Kelly Printing Co}, 1933 (Box-folder 24/26)
    - Pacific Typesetting Suit, 1923-1930 (Box-folder 24/27)
    - {Letters about payment and membership}, 1923-1935 (Box-folder 24/28)
    - J.M. Murray-Expenses 1919 Lockout, 1920 (Box-folder 24/29)
    - Murray "Typo Topics" I.T.U. Journal, 1929 (Box-folder 24/30)
    - {Letters about Minerva Mecum's membership}, 1928-1935 (Box-folder 24/31)
    - C.T. Moore vs King County Medical Service, 1934 (Box-folder 24/32)
    - Official Bulletin Seattle Typographical Union No. 202, 1926-1937 (Box-folder 24/33)
    - Peoples' Daily Newspaper, 1936 (Box-folder 24/34)
    - Seattle Post Intelligencer Arbitration on Wages due nine members H.L. Messegee, 1929-1935 (Box-folder 24/35)
    - {Account withdraw request and Vlahovich, John}, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 24/36)
    - Wynter, Harry, 1937 (Box-folder 24/37)
    - Napoleon Bureau, 1924-1926 (Box-folder 24/38)
    - Special Assistance and Reconstruction Report to International Typographical Union, 1925-1928 (Box-folder 24/39)
    - {Resolution for Seattle Typographical Union and booklets about Bylaws}, 1904-1934 (Box-folder 24/40)
    - Secy I.T.U. Members' Deaths Correspondence, 1931-1935 (Box-folder 24/41)
    - To- Arthur G. Bell -From, 1930-1931 (Box-folder 24/42)
    - Filed Wrong {Letters from Seattle Typographical Union}, 1927-1935 (Box-folder 24/43)
    - Misc. {Letters about contracts and membership status}, 1916-1937 (Box-folder 24/44)
    - Escrow Account- Label Promotion Asst- 41 Appellants, 1933 (Box-folder 24/45)
    - Correspondence, 1929-1937 (Box-folder 24/46)
  - SERIES X: GRIEVANCE FILES, 1905-1960 (Box-folder 25/1-25/65)
    - W.H. Salyer, Charges and Trials Results, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 25/1)
    - Tarbox, Michael, 141206 909 W. 92nd St. Discipline Case, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 25/2)
    - Greenlee, Clyde, 136635 Charges to Discipline Committee, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 25/3)
    - Goll, J.F. 141305, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 25/4)
    - Hardenbrook Case W. Olson, 1961 (Box-folder 25/5)
    - Hardenbrook Case W. Olson- Standing Committee, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 25/6)
    - Charges Ballard News Chapel, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 25/7)
    - Kaneko Appeal, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 25/8)
    - 5 1/2 Day Rule, 1930 (Box-folder 25/9)
    - Five Day Week, 1930-1931 (Box-folder 25/10)
    - Standing Committee --Hardenbrook, Seattle Times 1961, 1961-1967 (Box-folder 25/11)
    - Grange 1963-1964 Overtime Case Appeal (Box-folder 25/12)
    - 6th Day Controversy, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 25/13)
    - "Indefinite", 1921-1931 (Box-folder 25/14)
    - Casey-Kurth, Undated (Box-folder 25/15)
    - Forgues vs Craftsman Chapel, 1949 (Box-folder 25/16)
    - Johnson (Don E) vs STU, 1905-1908 (Box-folder 25/17)
    - Joss Charges, 1956 (Box-folder 25/18)
    - McLaughlin, BJ vs STU (Geo Roberts) Case #2, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 25/19)
    - Misaege vs Boss, Young, 1955 (Box-folder 25/20)
    - Hammer, OC Case, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 25/21)
    - McLaughlin, JB vs Imeson Case #1, 1947-1949 (Box-folder 25/22)
    - Thornton Appeal 5- Day Week Assessment, 1914-1916 (Box-folder 25/23)
    - Williams vs Seattle Times Archie E (day's pay), 1949-1950 (Box-folder 25/24)
    - McLaughlin, BJ Appeal, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 25/25)
    - McLaughlin- May 1949 Working Card, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 25/26)
    - BJ McLaughlin 3rd Case, 1946-1949 (Box-folder 25/27)
    - McLaughlin, BJ Appeal 4th case (Williams priority), 1949-1950 (Box-folder 25/28)
    - Exec Comm vs McLaughlin 5th case (slide day), 1949-1950 (Box-folder 25/29)
    - McLaughlin, BJ vs STU (overtime) case #6, 1950 (Box-folder 25/30)
    - Strike Committee, 1923 (Box-folder 25/31)
    - Appeal- 3% La Pro Assit. Fred Moorman et al against action 202, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 25/32)
    - Sandbeck Charges, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 25/33)
    - Taylor, I vs STU, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 25/34)
    - R.M. Johnson, et al vs #202 12 "Retained Employees" -P.J., 1925-1932 (Box-folder 25/35)
    - Wood, JB, 1950 (Box-folder 25/36)
    - Staton, Geo., 1950 (Box-folder 25/37)
    - Brewer vs. STU #202, 1951 (Box-folder 25/38)
    - Hershey, W.H. vs STU, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 25/39)
    - Aller vs Economy Comm, 1951 (Box-folder 25/40)
    - Ferris Appeal, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 25/41)
    - Lansing Appeal (OT), 1949 (Box-folder 25/42)
    - Flaig, JA vs STU, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 25/43)
    - Johnson, Don E Case, 1905-1912 (Box-folder 25/44)
    - Rieman - Star, 1944 (Box-folder 25/45)
    - Craftsman Press (Cromwell), 1945 (Box-folder 25/46)
    - Monte Branch vs Times (Availability), 1942-1943 (Box-folder 25/47)
    - Crossman - Star, 1944 (Box-folder 25/48)
    - DuBois Appeal, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 25/49)
    - Roy J McLaughlin Appeal, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 25/50)
    - Charges - H.L. Messegee vs Carl Torkelson, 1907-1930 (Box-folder 25/51)
    - STU #202 vs International Typographical Union Executive Council (O.S. Jones Decision), 1932-1933 (Box-folder 25/52)
    - Charges - H.L. Messegee vs M.E. Torell, 1930 (Box-folder 25/53)
    - Thomas Brown vs Platt, 1929 (Box-folder 25/54)
    - A.P. Holland, 1927 (Box-folder 25/55)
    - C.W. Jones' (re- Dues- assistants), 1931-1932 (Box-folder 25/56)
    - Mildred Roche vs STU #202, 1932 (Box-folder 25/57)
    - Skinner Appeal, 1939 (Box-folder 25/58)
    - Geo. Davis vs STU #202 to Executive Council ("Dirty" Moore Priority Base), 1929-1930 (Box-folder 25/59)
    - Cumingham vs Star Chapel Amiott discharge, 1931 (Box-folder 25/60)
    - Schott Discharge, 1931 (Box-folder 25/61)
    - Contract Violation by Times, 1930 (Box-folder 25/62)
    - Sovereign Appeal, 1940 (Box-folder 25/63)
    - Jackson Talbott- Appeals, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 25/64)
    - Koerber - Forbes, 1938 (Box-folder 25/65)
  - SERIES XI: CONTRACT NEGOTIATIONS, 1892-1980 (Box-folder 26/1-41/22)
    - 1943 Job Scale, 1938-1945 (Box-folder 26/1)
    - 1929 News Scale, 1917-1930 (Box-folder 26/2)
    - 1929 Arbitration, 1926-1935 (Box-folder 26/3)
    - 1942 Job Scale, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 26/4)
    - 1941 Job Scale, 1937-1944 (Box-folder 26/5)
    - 1926 Job Scale, 1925-1931 (Box-folder 26/6)
    - 1935 Job Scale (Box-folder 26/7)
    - 1937 Job Scale, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 26/8)
    - 1938 Job Scale, 1937-1944 (Box-folder 26/9)
    - Allied Printing Trades Council, Part 1 of 2, 1936-1944 (Box-folder 26/10)
    - Allied Printing Trades Council, Part 2 of 2, 1936-1944 (Box-folder 26/11)
    - 1944 Job Scale, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 26/12)
    - 1945-1946 Job Scale Negotiations (Box-folder 26/13)
    - Job Scale 1947, 1943-1947 (Box-folder 26/14)
    - Job Scale Nov 1, 1946 to Oct 31, 1947, 1935-1947 (Box-folder 26/15)
    - Job Shops Lockout, 1944-1948 (Box-folder 26/16)
    - 1953 Job Scale, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 26/17)
    - 1954 Job Scale, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 26/18)
    - American Weekly Controversy, 1921-1923 (Box-folder 26/19)
    - Newspaper Scales 1911-1920, 1907-1923 (Box-folder 26/20)
    - 1919 Arbitration (Box-folder 26/21)
    - 1921 Arbitration, Part 1/2, 1920-1923 (Box-folder 26/22)
    - 1921 Arbitration, Part 2/2, 1920-1923 (Box-folder 26/23)
    - 1924 Seattle Post Intelligencer Arbitration and News Scale, 1917-1926 (Box-folder 26/24)
    - 1923 News Scale, 1922-1923 (Box-folder 26/25)
    - 1926 News Scale, 1926-1928 (Box-folder 26/26)
    - Newspaper Scale, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 26/27)
    - Newspaper Scale, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 26/28)
    - Newspaper Scale Agreements, 1941-1943 (Box-folder 26/29)
    - Newspaper Scale, 1941-1943 (Box-folder 26/30)
    - Newspaper Contract, 1939-1941 (Box-folder 26/31)
    - Newspaper Contract, 1939-1941 (Box-folder 26/32)
    - Newspaper Scale Agreement, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 26/33)
    - PI, Star and Times Contract, 1933-1935 (Box-folder 26/34)
    - PI Contract, 1923-1928 (Box-folder 26/35)
    - Arbitration Agreements and Scales, 1904-1943 (Box-folder 26/36)
    - Printed Scales, 1892-1926 (Box-folder 26/37)
    - Lansing Appeal, 1938 (Box-folder 27/1)
    - Goodrich- Scott Appeal, 1941-1943 (Box-folder 27/2)
    - Attebery Appeal, 1941 (Box-folder 27/3)
    - Cunningham Appeal, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 27/4)
    - #202 vs Nero Rieman, 1941-1943 (Box-folder 27/5)
    - Nero-Rieman Appeal, 1941 (Box-folder 27/6)
    - Neubert Appeal, 1939-1943 (Box-folder 27/7)
    - Larkin, et al Appeal, 1934-1938 (Box-folder 27/8)
    - NW Envelope Co.- McDonald Investigating Comm, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 27/9)
    - Winans vs Seattle Typographical Union 202 (Ferris Discharge), 1926-1929 (Box-folder 27/10)
    - RL Cunningham vs STU 202 (Fred Smith Discharge), 1932 (Box-folder 27/11)
    - Witt Case, 1942 (Box-folder 27/12)
    - Landreth Appeal, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 27/13)
    - Schrupp Appeal, 1937-1939 (Box-folder 27/14)
    - Appeals- Discharge Cases -- Beckwith Appeal to Exec. Council (Chas. Taylor Discharge Case), 1932-1951 (Box-folder 27/15)
    - Charges Non-payment of Relief Assessments - Executive Committee DG Cloud, Part 1 of 4, 1933 (Box-folder 27/16)
    - Charges Non-payment of Relief Assessments - WM Conger by Executive Committee #202, Part 2 of 4, 1931 (Box-folder 27/17)
    - Charges Non-payment of Relief Assessments - Executive Committee vs W.M. Conger, Part 3 of 4, 1932-1933 (Box-folder 27/18)
    - Charges Non-payment of Relief Assessments - Appeal O.S. Jones- 3% Relief, Part 4 of 4, 1932-1933 (Box-folder 27/19)
    - L.C Campbell, G.W. Grothe, J.F. DuBois vs Times Chapel "Priority", 1932 (Box-folder 27/20)
    - Charges: Exec. Comm vs. Goodrich, B.E., 1935-1938 (Box-folder 27/21)
    - Charges- E.C. Oliver, 1933-1934 (Box-folder 27/22)
    - Charges: Executive Committee vs. L.H. Whittey, 1932 (Box-folder 27/23)
    - J.R. Sovereign vs Executive Committee (Election Seattle Post Intelligencer Chairman matter), 1932 (Box-folder 27/24)
    - Archie J. Little Charges, 1948 (Box-folder 27/25)
    - Charges- Executive Committee vs Paul Clemens, 1934 (Box-folder 27/26)
    - Ashton, et al vs STU #202, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 27/27)
    - Cooper, WL vs STU #202, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 27/28)
    - Arvid M. Bradley vs #202 (to Executive Committee), 1935 (Box-folder 27/29)
    - Morin Case, 1940 (Box-folder 27/30)
    - Woolley, HW Appeal, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 27/31)
    - Larkin Appeal, 1943 (Box-folder 27/32)
    - Brown, L.W. Appeal, 1917-1943 (Box-folder 27/33)
    - Steen vs Times Appeal, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 27/34)
    - Post-Intelligencer vs Seattle Typographical Union (Amsberry), 1944-1945 (Box-folder 27/35)
    - #202 vs Atteberry, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 27/36)
    - Martin vs Star (Mrs. Deming Priority), 1936 (Box-folder 27/37)
    - Sovereign,J.R. vs #202 (1933 Newspaper Scale), 1933-1934 (Box-folder 27/38)
    - Ashby Appeal to Executive Committee, 1939 (Box-folder 27/39)